firehousesubs.com 2008-06-23

# Firehouse Subs ® Privacy Policy

  |  |   
---  
|   |  |  | 

### Privacy Policy

FIREHOUSE SUBS  
WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

**Privacy Policy**

We are Firehouse Restaurant Group, Inc. Your privacy is important to us, which is why we have developed this online “Privacy Policy” to explain our practices regarding the use and disclosure of personally identifiable information we obtain online from users of our family of Websites, located at www.firehousesubs.com, and its [their] related links, webpages and content we own or control (“FIREHOUSE SUBS® Sites”). If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please send us an email (writing “Privacy Policy” in the subject line) at privacy@firehousesubs.com at 3410 Kori Road, Jacksonville, Florida 32257; or call us at (904) 886-8300. If for any reason you feel that we have not followed our stated policy, please tell us by e-mail at privacy@firehousesubs.com. We will look into your concern and try to resolve any problem. In the future, we may modify our web site policies. Please check this page for any changes. 

**Collecting Information**  
In general, through our FIREHOUSE SUBS® Sites, we take reasonable steps to avoid collecting any personally identifiable information from anyone unless that person specifies it or it’s provided by someone else. For example, you might be asked to voluntarily give your name, postal address, email address and phone number, and credit card or Pay-Pal Information to us when, if to the extent possible, via the FIREHOUSE SUBS® Sites, you purchase products from our FIREHOUSE SUBS® Sites, provide feedback on our products, apply for a job online or fill out a franchise questionnaire. We may also collect and store statistics and other information about the online activities of our visitors on an aggregate basis. 

**How we collect information about you. We collect information in 3 ways:**  
1\. We collect information that our customers or visitors to FIREHOUSE SUBS® Sites (including you) supply to us.

2\. We collect information from emails and other contacts sent to us by you, other customers and users of the FIREHOUSE SUBS® Site.

3\. We collect information electronically on all users of our website, including customers, by means of cookies.

**Types of personal information we may collect from you and other users.**

**1\. Product Purchases:**  
Every time you use the FIREHOUSE SUBS® Site to purchase goods or services, we may collect information about the FIREHOUSE SUBS® restaurants you select and the orders you place.

To obtain services from the FIREHOUSE SUBS® Site, you may be required to provide us with your full legal name, email address, full street address including city, state and zip code, and telephone number. And, to obtain certain services from the FIREHOUSE SUBS® Site, you may also be required to choose your “username” and /or “password” and provide those to us.

At some our FIREHOUSE SUBS® Sites, you may also be able to submit information about other people. For example, while most of our FIREHOUSE SUBS® Sites do not engage in on-line sales, you might be provided the option of ordering a gift, gift certificate or any products or service online. To do so you may be required to provide us personally identifiable information. For example, when you place an order with us by telephone or means other than our online ordering service, you may be required to provide us with your full legal name, full street address including city, state and zip code, and telephone number. When or if you place an order through the FIREHOUSE SUBS® Site, you may want the item purchased sent directly to the recipient; therefore, you might submit the recipient’s name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages may include: recipient’s name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number. It is also possible that someone may provide us with your personally identifiable information, with or without your permission.

**2\. Promotions:**  
We, or though third-party merchants, vendors and others we designate, may offer users of the FIREHOUSE SUBS® Site special offers, contests or other promotions (“Promotions”), we may provide to them the means via our website, mail, or email to contact you about our or their Promotions. However, if you have opted not to receive e-mails or other communications from us, we will make reasonable efforts not to provide your e-mail address, mailing address or other data or information to any third party for promotional or other commercial purposes, except with your prior consent. 

You are under no obligation to respond to any Promotion but if you do, you may be required to provide additional information, such as your birth date and whether you or anyone in your household is employed by the merchant who is extending the offer, in order to verify your eligibility for accepting the offer or participation in the Promotion. For any such Promotion, your provision of information to us or the merchant may be governed by the merchant's privacy policy, not our privacy policy.

**3\. Third-Party Information:**  
For reasons such as improving your experience at our FIREHOUSE SUBS® Site or personalizing our FIREHOUSE SUBS® Site to you (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we may supplement the information that you provide with information from third parties. 

**4\. Information Regarding Children:**  
Online ordering, customer registration for on-line ordering, and customer feedback pages of the FIREHOUSE SUBS® Site are directed toward and designed for use only by persons aged 13 or older. We do not establish or maintain registrations for any child whom we know to be under the age of 13. We do not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If we discover or are made aware that we have received personally identifiable information from an individual who indicates that he or she is, or whom we otherwise have reason to believe is, under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our systems. 

**5\. Use of Cookies:**  
Like many websites on the Internet, our FIREHOUSE SUBS® Site uses “cookies” – small strings of data placed on users' personal computer hard drives during the exchange of data that happens when your browser points to our website. Cookies enable a website to identify a user's browser as a previous visitor by means of a unique string of numbers assigned on a previous visit. Our cookies assist us in collecting information on what pages of our website you access or visit, and in recording any preferences you indicate on our website.

Our cookies cannot and do not retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses. If you are just browsing our website, a cookie identifies your browser and user ID (and not your identity). If you place orders with us, we use cookies to assist in storing your preferences and recording other session information (a "session" is a single visit by you to our website).   
****  
We store the information you provide to us and the information we collect electronically in our computer databases. We own, maintain and operate our computer servers containing our databases or may lease the use of such equipment and services from others. Access to our computer servers is controlled by security gatekeepers and firewalls. 

**How we use the information we collect.**  
Generally speaking, we make reasonable efforts to not share your personally identifiable information with outside third parties whose practices are not covered by this privacy policy without your permission. However, to serve you better we may share information about you with independently owned and operated FIREHOUSE SUBS® franchisees, state regulators, or product vendors and others we deem necessary.

We use the personal information about you stored in our member database in various ways. First, the next time you use our online ordering service, we may require you to enter your User ID and Password. If you do so, we may call up your information from our database to make processing your order faster and easier.

When you use any product or service ordering feature, or any account you may create on the FIREHOUSE SUBS® Site, we may also keep track of your food preferences and restaurant choices and analyze that information. We may do so in order to be able to email to you Promotions.

We also use the personal information about you stored in our customer database through telephone and other non-online orders in various ways. Each time you place an order, we may call up your information from our database to make processing your order faster and easier. We may also use the information to contact you concerning your level of satisfaction with our products and services, to verify incomplete orders, rectify problems or delays with your order or otherwise communicate with you concerning your transactions with us.

We may provide your personal information to our restaurant affiliates and franchisees in order to enable your local FIREHOUSE SUBS® restaurant(s) to better serve you. We also aggregate information about how our online ordering service is used (without specific identification to any particular user) to be able to improve our service and make it more responsive to our customers' preferences. We also make such aggregate information (without identification to any specific individual) available to our franchisees, vendors, strategic business partners, our affiliates and other businesses we choose in order to obtain information about products, services, offers and notices which we believe will be useful and informative to our website users.

**You can control how information about you is used.**  
You can also limit our communications directly to you. If you do not want to receive emails from us or relating to other Promotions in the future, you can opt out at any time by following the “Please remove me from your mailing list” link that is included in all automated subscriptions from FIREHOUSE SUBS®. Our emails to stop immediately after you click the link.

We and our franchisees may from time to time send nonpromotional email to all registered users of our online ordering service for the purpose of gathering and dispersing data to provide better services to our customers. Except for provision of additional information necessary to complete a transaction initiated by a registered user, registered users will be under no obligation to reply or answer questions in said nonpromotional email. Nonpromotional email may include, but will not be limited to, surveys, maintenance notices, system updates and confirmation or other notices in connection with completion of a transaction initiated by a registered user.

**Our policies may change.**  
This is our current Privacy Policy, but we reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and the FIREHOUSE SUBS® Site at any time. You should check the Privacy Policy periodically. If our policies regarding collection, storage and use of your information changes, the information collected under prior policies will continue to be governed by those policies, unless we obtain your consent to use that information in new ways. 

**You can access your information.**  
Upon your request, we will provide you with access to your unique account-related information and information from contacts that we maintain about you (“Your Account Information”). In your request, please provide us with your current specific contact information so that we can accurately check our records.

How is my information protected?  
Your Account Information is password-protected. In order to maintain this protection, we caution you not to provide your password to anyone. We do not give your password to anyone. We recommend that, if you share your computer with other people, you close your browser window when your session is completed. Signing off will protect your information if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library.   

---|---
